bodyinmind.com 2019-06-15

# BiM Privacy Policy

Privacy policy

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

Bodyinmind.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. technical support. 

**Email Addresses**

Bodyinmind.com has a strict no spam policy. Emails will be used only in reply to direct correspondence or to fulfil requested services, e.g. newsletter. Names, email addresses or any personal information will never be shared with 3rd parties for any purpose.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us at [support@bodyinmind.com](mailto:support@bodyinmind.com): 

• See what data we have about you, if any. 

• Change/correct any data we have about you. 

• Have us delete any data we have about you. 

• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.   

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. We do not collect or store sensitive information (such as credit card data) on our servers, that information is encrypted and transmitted directly to our payment processors in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Registration**

In order to enjoy the paid content on this website, a member must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information may be used to contact you about the products/services on our site only about which you have expressed interest.

**Cookies**

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the site. Cookies are also used to keep track of your choices of membership options when submitting forms to our payment processors. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. We do not use cookies to track user preferences on site & do not share such information with any 3rd parties at any time. 

**Surveys & Contests ** From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

© 1997-2018 Body in Mind. All rights reserved.
